hotels-rates.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy Policy - Hotels-Rates.com

Hotels-Rates.com places our greatest value on the relationship we have with our customers.

We are committed to protecting your personal privacy and the information you entrust with us. 

We will not ask you for information that does not have a purpose and we will not require information to be disclosed that is not absolutely necessary. 

Any information obtained by Hotels-Rates.com will not be shared with any third parties with the exception of the booking engine used to make your reservations. All of our data is kept private within the company. We will not disclose personal information except to appropriate authorities as required by law. 

Here is more specific information that we have to collect and the reasons why we do it: 

We need to have your name, email address, physical address, phone number and credit card number to ensure that we are able to make and confirm your reservation. We do not share this personal information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete your reservation. At most hotels, it will then be held until you can pay in person. 

This type of contact information is necessary in order to notify you in the event of difficulties or unforeseen obstacles fulfilling your reservation. In some cases, paper tickets may need to be mailed to you. Therefore, the easier we can make contact with you, more in tune we can be in serving you.

We will use the information you provide about yourself in order to make the Hotels-Rates.com website as user friendly as possible. We want to know you to better serve you. From time to time we may ask you for more information about your travel interests. Or offer you an opportunity to voice your opinion by taking a surveys. In the future this information may be used to help us make more applicable travel recommendations including destinations. However, this information will always be optional.

We understand that for you to take full advantage of the benefits of this interactive medium, we must do what we can to ensure that your privacy is secure and that the privacy of others is respected. And also use some generic information that is non-personal to improve the users experience.

Hotels-Rates.com may from time to time, include information about your visit in collective or aggregated data that does not identify you specifically. For example, we may tell our advertisers or investors the number of site visitors or the most popular vacation destinations. But there is no personal information given out.

Via our servers, we are able to recognize domain names and the pages that are visited in at specific times. This data is then gathered in an aggregate manner for quality control and the perpetual improvement of our site. This will help enhance your experience and keep you coming back! 

This may or may not include:  
  
Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates.

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links/Advertising  
This site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Hotels-Rates.com is in no way responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our customers to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Hotels-Rates.com website.

Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement, the practices of Hotels-Rates.com, or your dealings with our web site, please contact us at: [........@hotels-rates.com](http://www.google.com/recaptcha/mailhide/d?k=01UoQTffvH7hVcPiYkIOi8Zw==&c=rzaMLBiQElrKi4HF6KU1jaTi8wtFjTJLtSOkw2NHQUw= "Reveal this e-mail address")

This Privacy Policy was posted on Hotels-Rates.com on July, 2001 update January 2011. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make any significant change to this policy, we will post notice of the change on Hotels-Rates.com for a period of at least six months after the change is implemented.
